A Finding Aid to the Frank Stella Papers, 1941-1993, bulk 1978-1989, in the Archives of American Art AAA.stelfran
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1966-1989, undated; Series 1; (Boxes 1-4; 3.25 linear feet)
  - Institutions and Organizations, 1973-1989, undated; 1.4
    - American Academy in Rome, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ARC, The Society for the Arts, Religion and Contemporary Culture, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Architectural League of New York, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Archives of American Art, Smithsonian institution, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Art-in-Architecture Program, General Services Administration, 1978-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Art in Embassies Program, Department of State, 1978-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Art Sources, Inc., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Artists Rights Society, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, Next Wave Festival, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Center for International Contemporary Arts, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - College Art Association, 1978-1984, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of Boston, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ft. Worth Art Museum, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Independent Curators Incorporated, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - International Ausstellung Köln, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Learning to Read Through the Arts Program, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts Medical Society, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey Center for the Arts, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Port Washington Public Library, 1983-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Portland Center for the Visual Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Resources for Artists with Disabilities, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Ronnie Peterson Memorial Foundation, 1979-1980, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Studio in a School Association, Inc., 1986-1989, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Vatican Judaica Exhibition in America, National Committee, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Very Special Arts, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Yaddo, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Legal, 1972-1991; 1.5
    - Garbage Ticket, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Lawsuit, Lynn Factor v. Frank Stella, et al., 1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Lawsuit, Motors Insurance Corp. a/s/o Miles Tinsmith Roofing v. Harriet Stella (automobile accident), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Lawsuit, Stella vs. Mazoh, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Real Estate (Norman St. studio, Bridgeport, Conn.; 126 E. 13th St.), 1984, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Speeding Tickets 1-3, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Speeding Ticket 4, Taghkanic, N.Y., 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Speeding Ticket, Croton-on-Hudson, N.Y., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Speeding Ticket, Dover Plains, N.Y., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Speeding Ticket, E. Fishkill, N.Y., 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Speeding Ticket, Millbrook, N.Y., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Speeding Ticket, Millerton, N.Y., 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Speeding Ticket, Mt. Vernon, N.Y., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Speeding Tickets, New York City, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Speeding Ticket, Vermont, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Suspension of Drivers License, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Unauthorized Reproductions, 1978-1989 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986; 1.6
    - Daniel Goldreyer, Ltd., conservation Proposals for "Lunnawola II," "Grondo I," and "#25 Cieszowa II" (with photographs of damage), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Nicaragua, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Poster Design for Attica; UNICEF; The Paris Review, 1974, 1984, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné, 1967-1982 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Permissions, 1981-1989; 1.7
    - Permissions for Reproduction, Publication, Recording, Broadcasting, A-Z, (2 folders; see also: Requests Denied-Publication Permissions), 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Political, 1979-1989, undated; 1.8
    - Bill Bradley Senatorial Campaigns, 1984-1989, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Carter/Mondale Re-election Campaign, 1979-1982, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Edward M. Kennedy Senatorial Campaign, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Edward J. Koch Mayoral Campaign, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Ken Lipper for City Council President Campaign, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Howard Metzenbaum Senatorial Campaigns, 1981-1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Walter Mondale Presidential Campaign, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Projects Proposed but Not Executed, 1982-1984, undated; 1.9
    - Chicago Project/Donald Young Gallery, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Equitable Building/David Whitney, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Pittsburgh Subway, 1982-1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Sacramento Mall, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Requests Accepted, 1980-1989; 1.10
    - Autographs, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Books, Posters, Etc. for Fundraising, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Information about Paintings, 1980-1988 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Interviews, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Meet Stella, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - New York Times, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Photographs, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Students and Writers Requesting Information, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Requests Denied, 1976-1989, undated; 1.11
    - Art Donations, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Art for Fundraising, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Assistant/Apprentice Inquiries, 1981-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Autographs, 1976-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Awards, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Book Proposals, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Collaboration Proposals, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Commissions, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Conservation, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Consulting, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Critique Work by Other Artists, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Proposals, 1977-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Film, Video, Television Proposals, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Financial Contributions, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Interviews, 1978-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Invitations, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
    - Juries, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Lectures, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - Loans of Artwork, 1979-1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Meet Frank Stella/Tour Studio, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, 1980-1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Publication/Reproduction Permissions, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Purchase Work by Stella, 1979-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Students Wanting Help, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Visiting Artist/Teaching Offers, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Writers Seeking Information, 1978-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Writing by Stella, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Schools, Colleges and Universities, 1972-1989; 1.12
    - Barnard College, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Brandeis University, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brown University, 1981, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Brown University, Bell Gallery, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hampden-Sydney College, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Harvard University, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Harvard University Press (contract for Working Space; see also: Series 3.1. Writings by Stella-Book, Working Space, Harvard University Press, Editorial Process), 1983, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Merrick Educational Center, Sandi Goldman's Class, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - New York University, New York Institute for the Humanities, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - New York University, Society of Fellows, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Phillips Academy, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Princeton University, 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1981-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith College Museum of Art, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Swain School of Design, William Crapo Gallery, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - University of California at San Diego, Stuart Collection, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - University of Colorado, Boulder, Conference on World Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - University of Lowell, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, Anderson Gallery, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Princeton University, 1954-1958, undated; Series 2; (Box 4; 0.25 linear feet)
  Princeton University papers document Stella's undergraduate years and record both university and personal business.
  - Course Materials, 1956-1958, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Papers and Related Notes, circa 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Examinations, 1957, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Thesis Proposal, Notes and Draft, circa 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Thesis, "Art in Western Christendom,", 1958 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - University Business, 1954-1958, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Personal Business, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Selective Service System, Student Deferment, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Letters from Mom, Letter from Dad, 1955-1958, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters from Friends, 1955, 1957, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pencil Drawings and Sketches (5 sheets), undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photographs of Student Work by Frank Stella, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Items, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Writings, 1968-1993, undated; Series 3; (Boxes 4 - 7; 2.3 linear feet)
  This series is organized into two subseries:
  3.1: Writings By Stella, 1968-1993, undated
  3.2: Writings About Stella, 1978-1987, undated
  - Writings By Stella, 1968-1993, undated; 3.1
    Writings by Frank Stella consist of manuscripts for articles, talks and lectures. Included are manuscripts and notes for the series of six lectures delivered during his tenure as Charles Eliot Norton Professor of Poetry, Harvard University, 1983-1984. Stella's Norton Lectures were published under the title Working Space by Harvard University in 1986; drafts, revisions, with correspondence relating to the editorial process are included. Among his notes are a notebook containing reminders, shopping lists, engagements, a few sketches and miscellaneous doodles; also, notes about materials, color, scale, and the Exotic Bird series; names, addresses, and phone numbers; mailing lists, invitation and guest lists.
    - Article on Kandinsky (originally published in French as "Commentaire du tableau Complelxité simple-Ambiguité" in the Center Georges Pompidou Kandinsky exhibition catalog, and later incorporated into his Norton Lecture on Kandinsky), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Article on Velázquez for the New York Times, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Article, Complex Surfaces, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Talk, "Surface and Scale," Art Institute of Chicago, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Talk, "Painterly Painting Today," College Art Association, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Norton Lectures, Harvard University, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
      - "Caravaggio," Text Delivered October 13 and Copy Marked for Projector Operator, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - "Caravaggio" Drafts and Revisions, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 41-42)
      - "Caravaggio" Text Delivered in San Antonio, Texas, March 18, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - "Madonna of the Rosary" Drafts and Revisions, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 44-49)
      - "Madonna of the Rosary," Text Delivered, November 9, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - "Annibale Carracci" Drafts and Revisions, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
      - "Annibale Carracci" Text Delivered, December 6, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - "Picasso" Drafts and Revisions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - "Picasso" Text Delivered February 6 and Copy Marked for Projector Operator, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - "A Common Complaint" Text Delivered, March 15, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - "A Common Complaint" Drafts and Revisions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
      - "The Dutch Savannah," Drafts and Revisions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - "The Dutch Savannah," Text Delivered, April 4, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
      - Illustration Ideas, undated; (color post cards and photograph) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Book, Working Space, 1982-1985, undated (Box 5)
      - Draft [texts of Norton Lectures], 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
      - Edited Manuscript, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Edited Manuscript (incomplete), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Galley, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Foreword (not used), undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Illustration Lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Harvard University Press, Editorial Process, (see also: Series 1.12: Harvard University Press), 1985-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Notes, 1972-1977, undated (Box 5)
        - Notebook, May 1972-circa 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
          (mainly notes, addresses, engagements, shopping lists; contains a few sketches noting paintings seen, installation, and exhibition posters; also figure study, human and lion heads, and miscellaneous doodles)
        - Materials, Color, Scale, Exotic Bird Series, circa 1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
        - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
          (things to do, list of lectures, itinerary, poster production procedures)
        - "Feudal Organization of Society" and "Gregory VII,", undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
          (according to Harriet Stella, these are not class notes, but something Frank wrote when helping with his son's homework)
        - Names, Addresses, and Phone Numbers, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
        - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
        - Invitation/Guest Lists, 1983-1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Corrected Page Proofs, Master Set, 1986 (Box 6 (sol))
  - Writings About Stella, 1978-1987, undated; 3.2
    Writings about Frank Stella include manuscripts for articles, exhibition catalogs, and a gallery talk
    - Articles (Box 7)
      - "Frank Stella: Estrella Fugoz de Deslumbrante Creatividad" by Edward L. Shaw, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Article for The Christian Science Monitor by Christopher Bowden, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - "Post-Painterly Abstraction" by William I. Homer, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs (Box 7)
      - Stella Since 1970 by Philip Leider, Fort Worth Art Museum, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
      - The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné, 1967-1982 by Richard H. Axsom, Introduction Corrected by Stella (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné, 1967-1982 by Richard H. Axsom, Draft of Catalog Entries (incomplete) (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné, 1967-1982 by Richard H. Axsom, Edited Text of Catalog Entries (Box 7, Folder 9-11)
      - The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné, 1967-1982 by Richard H. Axsom, Exhibition Checklist and Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Frank Stella, Paintings 1958-1965: A Catalogue Raisonné by Lawrence Rubin, Manuscript with Corrections and Comments by Stella, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Frank Stella, 1970-1987 by William S. Rubin, Museum of Modern Art, First Draft, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Frank Stella, 1970-1987 by William S. Rubin, Museum of Modern Art, Edited Manuscript (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Frank Stella, 1970-1987 by William S. Rubin, Museum of Modern Art, Checklist, Bibliography, Chronology, and Illustration List (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Frank Stella, 1970-1987 by William S. Rubin, Museum of Modern Art, Galley Sheets (Box 6 (sol))
- Interview Transcripts, 1964-1993, undated; Series 4; (Box 7; 0.25 linear feet)
  Interview Transcripts represent published and unpublished interviews with Stella recorded for a variety of purposes. The interview with Philip Leider touches on many issues in contemporary art, and mentions Stella only briefly.
  The transcripts are arranged chronologically.
  - Interview with Frank Stella by Henry Geldzahler, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Tape Recorded Interview with Frank Stella," by Sidney Tillim for the Archives of American Art, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "A Conversation with Frank Stella by Nancy E. Miller,", 1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "Frank Stella-interview by Claude Gintz-October 25, 1979" (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "Interview with Frank Stella Regarding the New Print Series 'Polar Coordinates for Ronnie Peterson,' in Basel, with Christian Geelhaar", May 10, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "GEO Magazine Interview between Emile de Antonio and Frank Stella,", 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "Conversation at the Frank Stella Studio, New York City, between Frank Stella and Chris Cook with regard to his Upcoming Exhibition at the Addison Gallery, 15 September 1982" (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "Frank Stella in Conversation with Pat Gilmour-New York, 26 September 1984" (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Interview with Frank Stella by Friedhelm Mennekes, circa 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Interview with Frank Stella by Sumi Hayashi, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Interview with Frank Stella by Denise Green, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Interview with Frank Stella by Sam Posey, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Interview with Frank Stella," by unidentified interviewer, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Interview with Philip Leider, Editor of Artforum, by Emile de Antonio, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    (about Clement Greenberg's essay on easel painting, conceptual art, retrospective exhibitions, abstract artists and politics, Henry Geldzahler's exhibition, pop art, and criticism)
- Sketchbooks, 1956-1968, undated; Series 5; (Box 8; 0.25 linear feet)
  This series contains ten volumes of sketches in pencil, ink, and colored markers; two volumes contain related notes.
  - Sketch Book, 1956-1957; (spiral bound) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sketch Book, circa 1965; (pocket sketch book with notes on new paintings, color, shape) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sketch Book, 1967?; (spiral bound) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sketchbooks, 1968; (2 vols.; spiral bound) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sketch Book, undated; (pocket sketch book with list of artists, notes on abstract composition) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sketch Book, undated; (spiral bound) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sketch Book, undated; (spiral bound) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sketch Book, undated; (disbound spiral volume) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sketch Book, undated; (perfect bound tablet) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Registers and Inventories, 1959-1983, undated; Series 6; (Box 8; 0.25 linear feet)
  Among the Registers and Inventories are copies of records kept by dealers, as well as Stella's own records. Some of these files may have been compiled when The Prints of Frank Stella: A Catalogue Raisonné 1967-1982 by Richard H. Axsom and William S. Rubin's catalogs for Stella's two retrospective exhibitions at The Museum of Modern Art were being researched. Texts of these catalogs are among Writings (Series 3.2.2).
  - Register of Paintings and Works in Mixed Media (#1-#455), 1959-1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Register of Drawings (#D-1 - #D-101), 1959-1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Stella Master Check Lists [of Prints], February 20, 1982 and April 22, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Castillo and Mirish, Inventory, 1959-1971, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Larry Rubin/Park Arts, Inventory, and Sales Records, 1959-1973 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Series Inventories (Brazilian Series, Circuits, Exotic Birds, Indian Birds, Polish Synagogues, Shards, and South African Mines), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Lists Compiled or Collected by Stella, 1969-1983, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Financial Records, 1972-1986; Series 7; (Boxes 8 - 12 4.0 linear feet)
  Banking records consist of statements and cancelled checks. Petty cash receipts document personal and business purchases and include routine expenses such as groceries and parking, as well as art supplies, travel and entertainment. Paid bills are for personal and professional expenses including supplies, fabrication charges, studio remodeling, rental of studio in Connecticut, shipping, and travel. Most are annotated with the date of payment and check number. Records regarding expenses incurred by Stella's race horses include veterinary bills, boarding and transportation charges, stud fees, racetrack entry fees and winnings.
  7.1: Banking, 1984-1986
  7.2: Paid Bills, 1972-1986
  7.3: Payroll, 1986
  7.4: Petty Cash, 1984-1986
  7.5: Race Horses, 1983-1985
  - Banking Records, 1984-1986; 7.1
    - Statements, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
    - Debit Notices, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
    - Credit Notices, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Deposits, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 23-25)
    - Check Stubs, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 26-29)
    - Check Stubs, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Cancelled Checks, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 3-8)
    - Cancelled Checks (Payroll), 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Statements, Debit Notices, Credit Notices, Deposits, Cancelled Checks, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Paid Bills, 1972-1986; 7.2
    - AA-AB, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ace Hardware, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
    - AD-American Airlines, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - American Express, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - American Lung Association-AR, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - AT&T, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - AU-BERL, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Berton Plastics, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - BET-BR, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Bugayer, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - BUX-CEN, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Ceramics, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - CH-CitiBank, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - CitiBank Visa, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Ken Cohen Photography, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - COL-COM, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Con Edison, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - CONC-D, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - E-FI, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Flying Tiger Lines, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - FO-GOF, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Good Rush, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - GR-GS, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Harvard Expenses, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Harvard Magazine-Harvard University Press, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Hertz, 1975-1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - HI-IND, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Insurance Premiums, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - J-L, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - M, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - NA-NEW J..., 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - New York Central Art Supply, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - New York City Parking Tickets, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - New York Post, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - New York Telephone, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 20-24)
    - New York Times-NI, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Norman St., Bridgeport, CT, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 26-28)
    - O, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - P, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - R-SC, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Shipping, Packing and Storage, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - SM-STA, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Stevdan Stationers, Inc., 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - STEVE-Swan Engraving Co., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Swan Laser Die Co., 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - SY-TAB, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Tallix, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - TAN-TN, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Tompkins Tooling Industries, Inc. (10-A1-I), 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)